imma.ie 2019-12-10

# Website Privacy Policy | IMMA

The Irish Museum of Modern Art recognises the importance of your privacy when visiting our website. IMMA does not collect personal information about you when you visit our website unless you volunteer this information when signing up to various mailing lists, when booking tours/talks/lectures, buying IMMA editions/publications or becoming an IMMA Member. Your personal information is only used for the purpose you have requested and is not transferred or given out for any other use.

**IMMA’s Privacy Policy is outlined below:** **  
**  
**Information and Uses**  
IMMA will not sell, share, or rent your information without your express consent. Please read our [Data Protection Policy](https://imma.ie/about/policies-and-reports/public-policies/data-protection-policy/ "Data Protection Policy") to find out more about our overall policy with regard to personal data.

During your visit to this website IMMA may collect information from you at several different points as follows:

**i. Registration for services**  
During registration for various services throughout our website you are required to give contact information (such as your name and/or email address). This information is used to provide the services that you have requested, or to contact you about the service on our site for which you have specifically expressed an interest.

We collect data in the following areas:

i)  **Booking for a Talk or Tour.** This data is securely processed by our ticketing company Ticketsolve. Please see further details below.

ii)  **Becoming a Member  **This data is collected by the IMMA website and is processed by IMMA. Credit Card processing is conducted via PayPal. Please see further details below.

iii)  **Booking tickets for an event**  This data is securely processed by our ticketing company Ticketsolve. Please see further details below.

iv)  **Signing up to our mailing list  **We use Mailchimp as our GDPR compliant marketing automation platform. By signing up to our emailing list(s) you acknowledge that the information you provide will be transferred to MailChimp for processing in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) and [Terms](https://mailchimp.com/legal/terms/). MailChimp make it easy for you to unsubscribe at any point, and to manage what we email you about.

v)  **Purchasing items from the IMMA Shop**  We use Shopify as our GDPR compliant shopping partner. You can read their [Privacy Policy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy) on their website.

We will only contact you in relation to the service you have requested and will not transfer your personal information for any other use without your express consent.

**ii. Submitting Credit Card Details  
**When you submit your credit card details to avail of the various services on our website we use a secure server which assures that the information is protected against unauthorised access.

For Membership processing we use PayPal as an approved, secure GDPR compliant processor in accordance with their [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/ie/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-prev#4). You will know you are entering information into PayPal by the url which will start with [www.paypal.com](https://www.paypal.com/)

For Ticketing we use Ticketsolve as a secure, GDPR compliant ticketing processor. You will know you are entering information into Ticketsolve by the url which will end with .ticketsolve.com (e.g. www.imma.ticketsolve.com or www.immatours.ticketsolve.com

For the IMMA Shop we use Shopify as a secure, GDPR compliant commerce processor. You will know you are entering information into Shopify by the url which will start with <https://www.theimmashop.com/>

In all cases you will know the server is secure by the presence of the letter ‘s’ in [https](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTPS).

**iii.Cookies**  
Like most websites, we use “cookie” technology on our website. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a website to the hard drive of your computer so that the site administrator may identify your computer and passively track its activities on the website. This unique number identifies your web browser to our computer system whenever you visit our site. We may place a “cookie” in the browser file of your computer, however the “cookie” itself does not contain any personally identifying information about you. The “cookie” does not track your personal information or provide us with any way to contact you, and the “cookie” does not extract any information off your computer. We use the “cookie” to provide functional information about your browser, allowing us to provide you with a better experience. We also use “cookies” to gather broad demographic information and general usage patterns about you and other users of our sites.

**iv.   ****Google Analytics  
**We use Google Analytics to analyse what pages are most interesting to our site users, and to measure volumes of traffic to the site. All of this data, including your IP address, is anonymized and is not personally identifiable, nor does it provide us with any way to contact you.

**Please contact us with any questions about this website privacy statement at:**

The Data Protection Officer  
IMMA  
Royal Hospital Kilmainham  
Military Road  
Dublin D08 FW31  
or email to  

Any changes that we make to our Website Privacy Policy in the future will be made on this page. The information on this page was last updated on 28 November 2018 to update information applicable to the new website.
